A Guide to the Robert W. Stewart Papers, 1970s-1990s
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
Robert W. Stewart Papers, 1970s-1990s
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
M 242
17 linear feet.
Robert W. Stewart
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for use without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Robert Welton Stewart donated one box of materials in 1987. Robert J. Hermsen donated the remaining materials in October of 1995.
Biographical/Historical Information
Robert Welton Stewart was an architect based in Richmond, Virginia. Born in 1937 in Kansas, Stewart grew up in Minnesota and North Carolina, where he graduated from Duke University. He then received a master's degree from Yale University's School of Architecture. While working as a designer-draftsman with Baskerville & Son and during his employment at David Warren Hardwicke & Partners, Stewart gained the experience he needed to open his own architectural firm, Interplan, in 1972. He died in 1994.
Embracing a modern style, Stewart focused on constructing and remodeling residences in Richmond. In 1992, the Historic Richmond Foundation honored Stewart with its Distinguished Preservation Award, which acknowledged his commitment to preserve Richmond's architectural heritage. Stewart's major projects include the Pavilion at Providence Hall for the Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Virginia Commonwealth University's Conference Center, the Master Plan of Stratford Hall in Westmoreland County, and Historic Christ Church in Lancaster County, and the north and south wings of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of numerous architectural drawings, photographs, slides, correspondence and office files related to projects undertaken by Robert W. Stewart from the late 1970s to the early 1990s. Most of these materials are architectural drawings of Richmond, Va. area residences. Other materials in the collection help document Stewart's involvement with historic preservation.
Arrangement
Arrangement
Materials are arranged in alphabeltical order.
Organization
The collection is divided into three series. The first section consists of office files and correspondence relating to his architectural commissions. The second section, housed in the scrapbook area of the department, is comprised of slides, negatives and photographs of some of his commissions and of other buildings of interest to Stewart. Many of these slides are of architecturally historic buildings. The last section is made up of architectural drawings and blueprints generated by Stewart's practice. These drawings are located in map case drawers #40-67.
Contents List
- Office Files and Correspondence 1974-1994
  - Accomack Co., Preston and Stewart 1990 (Box 1)
  - AIA Honors Committee 1979-1989 (Box 1)
  - American Canals 1975 (Box 1)
  - Analysis of James River Flood Problems 1973 (Box 1)
  - Anderson House, Pierce Residence (9013/9212) 1991 (Box 1)
  - APVA 1992 (Box 1)
  - APVA 1992 (Box 1)
  - APVA Richmond Hill Notes 1990 (Box 1)
  - APVA Awards 1993 (Box 1)
  - APVA Belle Isle 1991 (Box 1)
  - APVA Board 1991 (Box 1)
  - APVA Board 1992 (Box 1)
  - APVA Branch Operating Manual 1987 (Box 1)
  - APVA Executive Committee 1992 (Box 1)
  - Fundraising 1992 (Box 1)
  - APVA Meeting Memos 1990 (Box 1)
  - APVA Old Stone House/Adam Craig House 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - APVA Property Inspection Reports 1990 (Box 1)
  - APVA Alterations to Outbuildings at 2300 E. Grace St. (9119) 1992 (Box 1)
  - Arrington, Marie Measured Drawings of 2709 E. Main St. 1992 (Box 1)
  - Barber, Jonnas, Goochland Co. Residence (9210) 1992 (Box 1)
  - Best Products 1984 (Box 1)
  - Biographical Notes from Interplan, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Blanton, Jack, 5412 Cary St. (9206) 1976 (Box 1)
  - Bolling Haxall House, Women's Club Brochure, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Bowles, Bowlman and Nancy, 11 Ampthill Rd. (9009) 1992 (Box 1)
  - Bradley, Gunter, 4704 Rolfe Rd. (9126) 1991 (Box 1)
  - Branch Library and Fire Station 1979 (Box 1)
  - Bristow, Robert, 11 Bridgeway Rd. (9304) 1993 (Box 1)
  - Broad Street Station Proposal (07602) 1976 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Alex (9131), n.d. (Box 1)
  - Brvan, John, 9 Tapoan Rd. (9202), n.d. (Box 1)
  - Byrd Airport, Proposal 1980 (Box 1)
  - Campbell, Edward, 101 Pepper Avenue (9218) 1991 (Box 1)
  - Carreras jewelers, Interior Design (9220) 1992 (Box 1)
  - Carter, Bryan, 6300 Three Chopt Rd. (9214) 1992 (Box 1)
  - Carter, Hill, 303 College St., Ashland (8306/9111) 1992 (Box 1)
  - Charlottesville, Industrial Development Authority 1992 (Box 1)
  - Central Richmond Association, Flood Prevention Committee 1978 (Box 1)
  - Church of the Good Shepard, Forest Hill Avenue at 43rd Street (Box 1)
  - Parish Hall Renovation 1992 (Box 1)
  - Downtown Streetscape Design Study 1976 (Box 2)
  - Downtown Riverfront/Downtown Streetscape 1976 (Box 2)
  - DeBoise, Mark 4122 Old Gun Road 1991 (Box 2)
  - Dixon Christian Window Contract, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Dogwood Dell Carillon (07604) 1977 (Box 2)
  - Dombalis Residence, 304 Sandalwood Dr. (9107) 1992 (Box 2)
  - Dujour Restaurant (8946) 1992 (Box 2)
  - Dujour Restaurant (8946) 1992 (Box 2)
  - East Coast Oil, 1420 Commerce Rd. Office Alterations (9108) 1991 (Box 2)
  - Eck, Francis, 2001 E. Franklin St., Rose Alley Restaurant (9118) 1991 (Box 2)
  - Egyptian Building/City Arena 1978 (Box 2)
  - Executive Mansion Renovations/Interplan Resumes 1990 (Box 2)
  - Fairfax Scale Office, Luck Stone Corp. (9036) 1992 (Box 2)
  - Feasibility Study for Bikeways in Richmond, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Flack and Krutz Consulting Engineers, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Flood Damage Survey, Main to James 1972 (Box 2)
  - Foreign Mission Board 07601 1976 (Box 2)
  - Founder's Hall Renovation, V.C.U. 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - Friends of Old City Hall, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Fulton Bottom Project, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Gottwald, Thomas, Addendum #2 (8917) 1990 (Box 2)
  - Gottwald, Bid by Martin Construction Co. 1990 (Box 2)
  - Gottwald, Door Schedule, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Gottwald, Field Measurements, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Gottwald, Window Alterations at 4502 Sulgrave Avenue, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Gottwald, Window Schedule 1989 (Box 2)
  - Gottwald, General Plans for 4502 Sulgrave (9102) 1991 (Box 2)
  - Gottwald, Transmittal Letters 1992 (Box 2)
  - Hamerick, Jim, Fredricksburg Apt. Project 1992 (Box 2)
  - Hamilton, Bernard, 4309 Cambridge (9033) 1992 (Box 2)
  - Hancock, Doris, 904 S. Gaskins Rd. (9216) 1992 (Box 2)
  - Hancock House, 11.5 North 29th St. 1990 (Box 2)
  - Hancock House, Correspondence 1990 (Box 2)
  - Hancock, John B., 5 Lorrain Station Rd. (9109) (Box 2)
  - Haverkampf, John 8043 Riverside Dr. (9117) 1991 (Box 2)
  - Hibbs Building, V.C.U., Food Services, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Houghtaling, Chet, 213 Wexleigh Lane (9134) 1991 (Box 2)
  - Howland, John, 15 Rio Vista Lane 1990 (Box 2)
  - Hyscop, John, 4321 Custis Road 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Implementation, Urban Historic Character, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Interior Elevationns, Site?, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Interplan, Prospective Clients 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Interplan, Proposals 1991 (Box 2)
  - Interplan, History and Project Listings 1990 (Box 2)
  - Interplan, Information Regarding Firm 1975-1979 (Box 2)
  - Interplan, Various Projects including Maymont, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Jones, Bob, Alterations to 19 Highland Rd. (9130) 1991 (Box 2)
  - Kendig, Mrs. Edwin L., 5008 Cary Street Rd. (9223) 1992 (Box 2)
  - Kephart, Kip, Caryhill (8953) 1991 (Box 2)
  - Kiptopeke State Park, Va. Division of State Parks 1992 (Box 2)
  - Lockgreen, Bill Davis Consulting Engineers (8736) 1988 (Box 3)
  - Luck Stone Corporation, Consulting (9132) 1992 (Box 3)
  - Luck Stone, Shop Drawings (9036) 1992 (Box 3)
  - Luck Stone, Shop Drawings (9036) 1992 (Box 3)
  - Luck Stone Specifications for Corporate Office (8802) 1987 (Box 3)
  - Luck Stone Specifications for Corporate Office (8802) 1987 (Box 3)
  - Luck Stone Specifications for Corporate Office (8802) 1988 (Box 3)
  - Making of Virginia Architecture, Charles Brownell's Memos 1989 (Box 3)
  - Masonic Temple Building/Temple Arts Center, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Master Format 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - Metro Richmond Chamber of Commerce 1974 (Box 3)
  - Midkiff, Charles, 10710 Cherokee Rd 1991 (Box 3)
  - Minor, Phillip, 303 Clovelly Rd. (9013/9015) 1990 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Proposals 1982-1988 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Proposals for Projects (includes background information on Interplan), n.d. (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Stationery, Fan District Association, n.d. (Box 3)
  - MNG Notes 1990 (Box 3)
  - Moore, Hullie, Consultation on New Residence (9043) 1991 (Box 3)
  - Moore, Hullie Consultation on Office Layout (9208), n.d. (Box 3)
  - Morgan, Elizabeth, 504 Honaker Ave. (9037) 1990 (Box 3)
  - Mount Vernon, Texas Gate 1987 (Box 3)
  - NASA, Langley Proposal 1977 (Box 3)
  - Navarre, Arnold, 5024 Sylvan Rd. (9027) 1983 (Box 3)
  - Neighborhood Assistance Act, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Newell, Samuel W., Jr. Specifications for residence at Drum Point, Lancaster County Virginia 1984 (Box 3)
  - Northsid Commercial Revitalization Plan (07901) 1979 (Box 3)
  - Northsid Commercial Revitalization Plan (07901) 1979 (Box 3)
  - Null, Cleveland, Red Oak Lane, Gettysburg, Pa (9205 1992 (Box 3)
  - NVAIA 1990 (Box 3)
  - Onancock Proposal (07607) 1977 (Box 3)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council 1992 (Box 3)
  - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council 1992 (Box 3)
  - Osborne, Susan, 609 Pine St. (9218) 1992 (Box 3)
  - Overnite Transportation Co, Annual Report 1976 (Box 3)
  - Pace-King House Renovation 1975 (Box 3)
  - Packer, Dr. and Mrs. Bernard D., Packer Beach House 1981 (Box 3)
  - Parrish, Jack and Betsy, 5324 Cary St. (9104) 1992 (Box 3)
  - Photographic Art Articles 1979 (Box 3)
  - Pierce, Wendy and Blackie Residence, Correspondence (9013) 1991 (Box 3)
  - Pierce Residence, Guest and Main House (9013) 1991 (Box 3)
  - Pierce Residence (9212) 1992 (Box 3)
  - Preservation Alliance of Virginia 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Preservation Alliance of Virginia, Board of Trustees 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Preservation Alliance of Virginia, Board Briefings 1992 (Box 4)
  - Preservation Briefs Newlsetter, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Preservation Briefs 2: Repointing Mortar Joints, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Priddy, Robert, 115 S. Wilton (9203) 1992 (Box 4)
  - Rappahannock Record Newspaper/Christ Church Reception Center 1975 (Box 4)
  - Restaurant Menus, Miscellaneous Faxes 1992-1993 (Box 4)
  - Resume's: Stewart, Harnsberger, Ostergren, Norman 1990s (Box 4)
  - Richmond Arts Magazine 1990 (Box 4)
  - Richmond City Branch Library/Richmond Fire Station 1979 (Box 4)
  - Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority 1978-1979 (Box 4)
  - Richmond's Secret Treasure Brochure, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Riley, Ann, 3449 West Cary St. (9228) 1992 (Box 4)
  - Ritchie, John, 2234 Monument Avenue Consultation (9215) 1992 (Box 4)
  - Riverfront 1977 (Box 4)
  - Riverfront Exhibition 1982 (Box 4)
  - Riverfront Notes 1970s (Box 4)
  - Riverfront Notes 1970s (Box 4)
  - Riverfront Pilot Project 1977 (Box 4)
  - Riverfront: Report Drafts to Edit, Canal, Brown's Island 1970s (Box 4)
  - Robins, Ann, Tappahannock Residence Consultation (9127), n.d. (Box 4)
  - Room Finish Schedule (8917), n.d. (Box 4)
  - Roosevelt Island 1975 (Box 4)
  - Sassafras: Space, Planning at 5808 Grove Avenue (9129) 1991 (Box 4)
  - Sauer, C.F., Consultation at Old Sears Building (9038) 1991 (Box 4)
  - Science Museum of Virginia 1970s (Box 4)
  - Science Museum of Virginia (07701) 1976 (Box 4)
  - Science Museum of Virginia, Notes 1977 (Box 4)
  - Scott, Robert T., 1 Robin Road (9124) 1992 (Box 4)
  - Scott Robert T., 1 Robin Road (9124) 1992 (Box 4)
  - Second Baptist Church, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Settle Notes, Pace-King? 1981 (Box 4)
  - Shockoe Slip Article/Shockoe Valley Plan 1984 (Box 4)
  - Sharp, Richard, Tennis Court at Entrance at Barrington West (9226) 1992 (Box 4)
  - Slabaugh, Raymond, III, Residence on Clovelly Road (9207) 1992 (Box 4)
  - Storefront Rehabilitation in Jackson, Mississippi, n.d. (Box 4)
  - State Offices Satellite Complex Proposal Plan (07605) 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - Strategy for Action for Downtown Richmond 1976-2000 (Box 4)
  - Stratford Hall Plantation (9106) 1970-1990 (Box 5)
  - Stratford Hall Plantation (9106) 1992 (Box 5)
  - Stratford Hall Plantation, Plantation Store Renovation (9305) 1992 (Box Box 5)
  - Stratford Hall Library (07606) 1976 (Box 5)
  - Stratford Hall, Storage Addition to Reception Center (9106) 1992 (Box 5)
  - Strafford Hall, Reception Center, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Summary of Findings for Richmond Local Flood Protection, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Syndor, Dancing Point (7002) 1987 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer Residence (8736) 1988 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer Residence (8736) 1989 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer Residence (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer, CADD File Index, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer Correspondence 1988 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer, Drawings 1988 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer, Easement Agreement 1988 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer, Memos and Notes 1988-1989 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer, Pool by JOPA 1988-1989 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer, Product Information 1988 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer, Product Information 1988 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer, Product Information and Specifications 1989 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer, Shop Drawings 1989 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer, Taylor and Parrish Certicficates for Payment 1989 (Box 5)
  - Thalhimer, Transmittal Letters 1988-1990 (Box 5)
  - Tysinger, Alicia, Entrance at 410 St. Christopher's Rd. (9209) 1992 (Box 5)
  - Urban Character (07502) 1975 (Box 6)
  - Urban Design Committee 1976-1977 (Box 6)
  - Urban Design Committee 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - Urban Historic Character/Conservation Plan, n.d. (Box 6)
  - University of Virginia, Observatory Dinning Hall 1982 (Box 6)
  - Vanishing and Returning Gardens of Richmond, Draft 1977 (Box 6)
  - Vanishing and Returning Gardens of Richmond, Draft 1977 (Box 6)
  - V.C.U. Projects 1978 (Box 6)
  - V.C.U. Proposal for the School of the Arts Building 1985 (Box 6)
  - V.I.P., 5th Street Team 1975 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Beach Center for the Arts 1982 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Children's Art Resource Center 1989 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Annual Report 1969 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Proposals 1965 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Poposed North Wing 1970 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, South Wing Opening Brochures 1970 (Box 6)
  - Williams, Julien and Lucy, 6429 Roselawn Rd. (9301) 1992 (Box 6)
  - Window and Doors at One Robin Rd. (9124) 1987 (Box 6)
  - Young, M.O., 4 Mike Tree Plantation (9022) 1990-1991 (Box 6)
- Slides, Negatives, and Photographs
  Various Found Negatives was written on the paper sleeve in which the negatives were found. There is no distinction between the term found negatives and what the compiler has referred to as miscellaneous negatives. Some negatives also included an architectural drawing number. These are referred to as Job #s. The negatives in this collection were in great disarray but attribution has at least been attempted where there was some indication of the job.
  - Slide 1, Kjellstrom and Lee Office (Box 7)
  - Slide 2-A, Stratford Hall Plantation (Box 7)
  - Slide 2-B, Stratford Hall Reception Center (Box 7)
  - Slide 2-C, Stratford Reception Center Plans (Box 7)
  - Slide 3, Syndor Residence (Box 7)
  - Slide 4, Interior of Unknown House, Massey/Holt Residence? (Box 7)
  - Slide 5, Scott Hingley (Blacksmith) (Box 7)
  - Slide 6, Robertson Residence (Box 7)
  - Slide 6-A, Unknown Residence, Robertson Residence? (Box 7)
  - Slide 7, Elmington (Box 7)
  - Slide 8, Unknown Residence, Chesterfield Co., Meiller Residence? (Box 7)
  - Slide 9, Fan District, 2041 West Grace Street? (Box 7)
  - Slide 10, C. F. Sauer Co. (Box 7)
  - Slide 11, Byrd Park Pumphouse (Box 7)
  - Slide 12, Unknown Row House (Box 7)
  - Slide 13, Layfield Site (Box 7)
  - Slide 14, Pace-King House (drawing 8709) (Box 7)
  - Slide 14-A, Pace-King House Plans (Box 7)
  - Slide 15, Richmond Coliseum and Blues Armory (Box 7)
  - Slide 16, Unidentified Jackson Ward Houses (Box 7)
  - Slide 16-A, Skylark Farm, Cheek Residence (Box 7)
  - Slide 17, Philip Morris Factory (Box 7)
  - Slide 18, F and M Building (Box 7)
  - Slide 19, Street Plans, Richmond (Box 7)
  - Slide 20, Barret House (Box 7)
  - Slide 21, Old Train Station (Box 7)
  - Slide 22, Broad Street and Downtown Buildings (Box 7)
  - Slide 23, Franklin Street Buildings (Box 7)
  - Slide 24, Kent-Valentine House (Box 7)
  - Slide 25, Fan District Houses (Box 7)
  - Slide 26, Masonic Temple/Richmond Free Press Building (7820) (Box 7)
  - Slide 27, Church Hill and Shockoe Districts (Box 7)
  - Slide 28, Providence Hall Model (Box 7)
  - Slide 28-A, Pleasant Hill (Box 7)
  - Slide 29, Unknown Residence, Goochland Co. (Box 7)
  - Slide 30, Unknown Residence (Box 7)
  - Slide 31, Miscellaneous Richmond Sites (Box 31)
  - Slide 32, Ivan Chermayeff Slides (Box 7)
  - Slide 33, Richmond Public Housing (Box 7)
  - Slide 34, Shockoe Slip Historic District (Box 7)
  - Slide 35, Visual Improvement Project 1975 (Box 7)
  - Slide 36, Adam Craig House (Box 7)
  - Slide 37, Paradise Park (Box 7)
  - Slide 38, Brookfield (Box 7)
  - Slide 39, 108 N. 1st Street, Robert Stewart Office (Box 7)
  - Slide 40, Unknown Residence, Saunders Interior Views? (Box 7)
  - Slide 41, Museo Nacional De Antropolgia (Box 7)
  - Slide 42, Roosevelt Island (Box 7)
  - Slide 42-A, Haskell Garden Room (Box 7)
  - Slide 43, Federated Arts of Richmond (Box 7)
  - Slide 44, Brooks and Womack Churches (Box 7)
  - Slide 45, Science Museum (Box 7)
  - Slide 46, California Trip 1979 (Box 7)
  - Slide 47, Stewart Residence (Box 7)
  - Slide 48, Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box 7)
  - Slide 49, V.C.U. and Hibbs Dining Hall (Box 7)
  - Slide 50, Jacks Residence (Box 7)
  - Slide 51, Coppedge Residence (Box 7)
  - Slide 52, Osdene Staircase (Box 7)
  - Slide 53, 2041 West Grace Street (Box 7)
  - Slide 54, Hilton Head 1974 (Box 7)
  - Scandinavia, Maudep 1974 (Box 7)
  - Slide 55-A, Copenhagen, Denmark (Box 7)
  - Slide 56, Limerick, Ireland (Box 7)
  - Slide 57, Fort Worth, Texas (Box 7)
  - Slide 58, Unknown House (Box 7)
  - Slide 59, Unkown Palladian Style House (Box 7)
  - Slide 60, Patterson Avenue School (Box 7)
  - Slide 61, Unknown Construction Site (Box 7)
  - Slide 62, Randolph Family Housing (Box 7)
  - Slide 63, Miscellaneous Chicago Buildings (Box 7)
  - Slide 64, Museum of Modern Art, New York (Box 8)
  - Slide 65, Sezincote, Gloucestershire (Box 8)
  - Slide 66, Unknown House Construction Site (Box 8)
  - Slide 67, Unknown City Buildings (Foreign) (Box 8)
  - Slide 68, San Francisco Trip 1975 (Box 8)
  - Slide 69, Saunder's Residence (Box 8)
  - Slide 0-29, Model of Unknown Building (Box 8)
  - Slide 0-30, Kjellstrom Residence (Box 8)
  - Slide 7837, O.H. Jones House Model (Box 8)
  - Slide 8010, V.C.U. Meeting House (Box 8)
  - Slide 8012, Bainbridge House (Box 8)
  - Slide 8056, Wright Residence (Box 8)
  - Slide 8308, Eskimo Pie Building (Box 8)
  - Slide 8336, Orami Temple (Box 8)
  - Slide 8632, Steele Residence (Box 8)
  - Slide 8715, Brent Residence (Box 8)
  - Slide 8799, Bob's House (Box 8)
  - Slide 9006, East Coast Oil (Box 8)
  - Slide 70, Rushden, Stratford, Rotterdam, Greenwich (Box 8)
  - Slide 70-A, London, British Museum, Windsor, St. Albans (Box 8)
  - Slide 70-B, Windsor Castle, Hampton Court, St. James, Holland, Coventry (Box 8)
  - Slide 71, Scotland: Edinburgh, Strirling, etc (Box 8)
  - Slide 73, Unknown Interior Office Space (Box 8)
  - Slide 74, Unknown Interior Views, Residential (Box 8)
  - Slide 75, Drawings of Unknown Plaza and Tunnel, Riverfront Project? (Box 8)
  - Slide 76, 5th Street Team Model 1975 (Box 8)
  - Slide 77, Virginia Beach Center for the Arts Site (Box 8)
  - Negative 43 (Job 8817), Hollywood Cemetery Intendents House (Box 8)
  - Negative 44 (Job 9033), Hamilton Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 45-A, Galeski Residence? (Box 8)
  - Negative 45, Galeski Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 46, Unknown Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 47, Edward L. Frost Co. (Box 8)
  - Negative 48, Unknown Sites (Box 8)
  - Negative 49, James River Front (Box 8)
  - Negative 50, Thalhimer Residence? (Box 8)
  - Negative 51, Unknown Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 52, Robertson? Perrins? Coppedge Residence? (Box 8)
  - Negative 53, Alex Brown and Son, Investment Banking? (Box 8)
  - Negative 54, Unknown Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 55 (Job 8416), Bryan Residence, 206 Greenway Lane (Box 8)
  - Negative 56, Uniquehorn?, Truesdale? (Box 8)
  - Negative 57, Pace King House/Adam Craig House (Box 8)
  - Negative 58 (Job 9005), Pool at Ballyshannon (Box 8)
  - Negative 59 (Job 8913), Unknown Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 60, Unknown Wooded Site (Box 8)
  - Negative 61, Unknown Fan House, Stratford Hall (Box 8)
  - Negative 62, Hull Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 64 (Job 9015), Minor Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 65 (Job 9019) (Box 8)
  - Negative 66 (Job 9026), Morse Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 67 (Job 9035), Asch Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 68 (Job 9012), Sauer's Residence? (Box 8)
  - Negative 69, Unknown Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 70, Digits Store at 1209 E. Cary St. (Box 8)
  - Negative 71, James River (Box 8)
  - Negative 72, Unknown Fan Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 73 (Jobs 8830 and 8736), Unknown Houses (Box 8)
  - Negative 74 (Job 9017), Seipel Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 75, Unknown Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 76 (Job 8743), Skylark Farm (Box 8)
  - Negative 77 (Job 9102), Gottwald Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 78, Unknown Sites (Box 8)
  - Negative 79 (Job 7540), Unkonwn Sites (Box 8)
  - Negative 80, Meiller Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 81, Unknown Lot, Butler Lot? (Box 8)
  - Negative 82, Unknown Addition, Stewart, Butler, Waverly Addition? (Box 8)
  - Negative 83, Brandon Church (Box 8)
  - Negative 84, Christ Church Reception Center, Irvington, Va (Box 8)
  - Negative 85, Robertson Residence/ 1523 West Avenue (Box 8)
  - Negative 86, Unknown Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 87, Broad Street Buildings (Box 8)
  - Negative 87-A, Unknown Site (Box 8)
  - Negative 88, Family/Friends (Box 8)
  - Negative 89, Unknown Interior (Box 8)
  - Negative 90, Unknown Office/Warehouse (Box 8)
  - Negative 91, Unknown Interior (Box 8)
  - Negative 92 (Job 8817) (Box 8)
  - Negative 94 (Jobs 8809, 8811?), Unknown House (Box 8)
  - Negative 95 (Job 8927), Virginia House (Box 8)
  - Negative 96 (Job 8907), Unknown Site (Box 8)
  - Negative 96-A, Unknown Site (Box 8)
  - Negative 97, Unknown Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 99 (Job 8943), Unknown Site (Box 8)
  - Negative 100 (Job 8940/3940) (Box 8)
  - Negative 101, Unkown Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 102, Unknown Downtown Richmond Building (Box 8)
  - Negative 103, Unknown Site (Box 8)
  - Negative 104, Unknown Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 105, Saunders Residence? (Box 8)
  - Negative 106, Goochland Co. Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 01 (job 8222), Linden Row Carriage House (Box 8)
  - Negative 02 (Job 8214), Sydnor Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 03 (Job 8221), Paul Spears Condos (Box 8)
  - Negative 04 (Job 7906), Scher Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative04-A, Beth-El Social Hall (Box 8)
  - Negative 05 (Job 8306), Hill Carter Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 06 (Job 8304), Heltzel Office (Box 8)
  - Negative 07 (Job 8308), Eskimo Building (Box 8)
  - Negative 08 (Job 8310), 2001 E. Franklin Street (Box 8)
  - Negative 09 (Job 8226), Garland Sydnor Residence (Box 8)
  - Negative 10 (Job 7901), Saunder Kitchen (Box 8)
  - Negative 11 (Job 7634), Wiltshire Residence, Goochland Co. (Box 8)